(Raj:)Now, where does your mom
keep the Crisco?
(Howard:)I don't know.
(Howard:)Probably in a wad in her cheek.
(Bernadette:)I'll help Raj in here.
Why don't you go keep my dad company?
Oh, he doesn't want me in there.
I'm the creepy little guy
(Howard:)who has sex with his daughter.
(Bernadette:)-Don't be silly, he loves you.
-Does he?
(Bernadette:)-Okay, he cares about you a lot.
-Really?
(Bernadette:)I do crap for you all the time.
Get out there.
(Howard:)So your wife's in Arizona
with the grandkids?
(Mike:)Uh-huh.
(Howard:)You know, my mom's been to Arizona.
(Howard:)She rode one of those mules
down in the Grand Canyon.
(Howard:)Long story short,
they had to shoot it.
Because she's so fat.
(Howard:)I'll get the door
while you finish laughing.